#### Contact

akhiljithk112@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/akhiljith-k (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Adobe XD

Express.js

Web Design

# Akhiljith K

Founder & CDO at GADS | Tech Enthusiast | UI/UX Designer | Web Developer

Trivandrum

## Summary

A tech enthusiast with ardent interest in web development. A good team player with excellent management skills. Experienced on product design, development and management along with superior and strong knowledge of UI/UX trends. A self learner with lot of passion towards development and technology trying to thrive in this digital world.

## Experience

**GADS** 

Founder & CDO April 2020 - Present (1 year 2 months)

ISTE Student Chapter GEC Barton Hill Webmaster June 2020 - Present (1 year)

### Education

Govt. Engineering College, Barton Hill, Thiruvananthapuram Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Information Technology · (2019 - 2023)

#### **ABVHSS**

PLUS TWO, Computer Science · (2017 - 2019)

Mother Teresa High School Muhamma SSLC · (2016 - 2017)